

CONTACT ME

778 - 814 - 7556 d.mcleod088@gmail.com 10738 133 St. #26, Surrey, BC PORTFOLIO:

https://donnaamm.github.io/portfolio/

SUMMARY

Highly creative, determined and motivated to provide high quality service and work. Efficient at ensuring all tasks and deadlines are completed in a timely manner. Continuous learner able to quickly adapt to changing work environments and technology. I am a problem solver with excellent time management aiming to find a suitable position to further develop my skills and experience and to help a company succeed.

SKILLS

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
After Effects
HTML/CSS
Photography

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

Graphic Design Technology Diploma Vancouver Career College, Surrey	2021-2022
Hairdressing, Diploma Hair Art Academy, Surrey	2012-2013
Responsive Web Design Certificate Freecampcode, Online	2022
Graphic Design Tips & Tricks Certificate Linkedin Learning, Online	2022

EXPERIENCE

LAILRICL	
Reception/Optometric Assistant/Lab Technician Langley Eyecare Centre, Langley	2015-2021
Hairstylist Champers Hair And Spa, Surrey	2014-2015
Hairstylist Prism Hair Designs, Langley	2013-2014
Cashier Green Timbers Liquor Store, Surrey	2012

Financial Customer Service Representative 2009-2012
Cash Store Financial, Surrey/Langley